Viewers all over the world, I say to you, be restored, in the name of Jesus!
I can see you being restored!
I can see your health being restored!
I can see your career being restored!
I can see your finances being restored!
I can see your business being restored!
Be restored!
Pray along with Prophet T.B. Joshua - Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
What is the position of your health? Are you on the sickbed?
Your liver, kidneys, blood, muscles, bones, tendons -
be restored, in the name of Jesus!
Pray along with Prophet T.B. Joshua - Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Any of your organs - be released, in the name of Jesus!
Any of your faculties - be released, in the name of Jesus!
Dry bones shall rise again!
Come back!
Say, come back!
My life - come back!
My business - come back!
My finances - come back!
My career - come back!
My destiny - come back!
My family - come back!
Come back!
By the power of resurrection, come back!
Pray along with Prophet T.B. Joshua - Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Listen, your destiny can never be changed!
If something happened to your destiny and you know that something has happened,
it means that you have abandoned your destiny and followed someone else's destiny.
Viewers, resurrection is to bring back your destiny
so that you can become an authority in your calling.
Right now, this an occasion!
Bring back my destiny!
If you are destined to be a fishermanm you'll become an authority in it.
If you are destined to be a carpenter, you'll become an authority at the end of the day.
If you are destined to be a vendor, you'll become an authority.
Right now, I pray, in the name of Jesus, be restored!
Be restored, in the name of Jesus!
Pray along with Prophet T.B. Joshua - Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
We believe that you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today,
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing Lives, Changing Nations, and Changing the World.